<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Useless Machines! (VMMF-2017)</title>
    <link>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Useless Machines! (VMMF-2017)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 22:26:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks!</title>
      <link>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/contact/thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 22:26:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/contact/thanks/</guid>
      <description>Thanks! We&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you as soon as we can - hopefully within a day.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t get a copy of your message within a few minutes, please try again and make sure you&amp;rsquo;ve entered your email address very carefully.
Home</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step 1: Wiring</title>
      <link>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/electrical/connect-electrical-parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 11:37:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/electrical/connect-electrical-parts/</guid>
      <description>Look at the bottom of the circuit board, under the blue terminal blocks.
One side is labeled for the batteries, the other for the motor. Also there are markings above for red and below for black wires.
The batteries are connected as labeled, but there is one trick for connecting the motor, explained next.    Before wiring the motor, look at your motor mount.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step 1: Test fit</title>
      <link>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/box-build/dry-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 22:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/box-build/dry-test/</guid>
      <description>Put the pieces of the box and lid together without glue so you can understand how the pieces fit.
If there are any black soot marks you don&amp;rsquo;t like, you can remove them with a clean pencil eraser.    These three &amp;lsquo;motor mount&amp;rsquo; pieces hold the motor, switches and the arm.     The hinge and battery holder holder parts go in later, once the box is glued.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kit Contents</title>
      <link>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/welcome/kit-contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 15:24:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/welcome/kit-contents/</guid>
      <description>The first thing you should do is unpack and organize the bag of wooden parts.    Notice that there is a burned side and a clean side to each part. You can choose what side you want to be the outside of the box.    Now separate your parts into groups:    Box    Lid    Motor mount    Battery holder holder    Hinges     Now it is time to assemble these parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step 2: Glue</title>
      <link>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/box-build/glue-wood-parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 22:52:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/box-build/glue-wood-parts/</guid>
      <description>First set out the box pieces like this.
Don’t include the top piece with the hole in it. The kit is easiest to assemble and maintain if this top piece is never glued in.    Make sure the sides you want on the inside are facing up.
Now put glue on the cracks.    Put glue on all the joint fingers except the six for the box top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step 2: Final Assembly</title>
      <link>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/electrical/final-assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:43:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanhugo.github.io/useless/electrical/final-assembly/</guid>
      <description>Start with the motor. Put the shaft in the slot like in the picture. The wires need to be away from the motor mount.    Turn the motor until the yellow plastic tab is in the slot in the end of the motor mount, and push the motor against this end wall.    There is a small yellow circle on the side of the motor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>